<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>3.029 Blog</title>
        <link>https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/announcements</link>
        <description>3.029 Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assignment 01]]></title>
            <link>https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/announcements/pset-01</link>
            <guid>https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/announcements/pset-01</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hey everyone,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey everyone,</p><p>Assignment 01 has now been posted to canvas, and will be due next Wednesday, 02/16 at 1PM.
As we discussed in lecture today, it should be fairly short - consisting of two problems (chaotic dynamical systems and normal modes on a ring).</p><p>A few additional announcements:  </p><ul><li>The <a href="https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/docs/intro#tentative-schedule-of-topics" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">syllabus</a> has been updated to reflect the tentative schedule of topics, as well as assignment due dates. Please check these against your other core DMSE classes, and let me know if there are any major conflcts - we can be flexible.  </li><li>Following the poll results, I will hold office hours on Mondays 4-5pm. I will update you once I have a room reservation.  </li><li>Similarly, our regularly-scheduled get-togethers will be Thursdays 8-9pm, starting this week 02/10. I will prepare for "Data-Viz Hour" (unless I hear from you that you prefer we introduce Jupyter notebooks), and again I will update you with the room once I have a reservation.</li></ul><p>See you on Wednesday for our first thermo-related lecture!<br>
<!-- -->George</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>psets</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome!]]></title>
            <link>https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/announcements/welcome</link>
            <guid>https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/announcements/welcome</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hey everyone,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey everyone,</p><p>Welcome to 3.029! The teaching team is very excited for this semester, and looks forward to meeting you and getting to know each of you better. </p><p>Our first lecture will take place tomorrow (Monday, 01/31) 1:00pm-2:30pm in room 4-261. A few important notes ahead of tomorrow:</p><ul><li><p>Lectures will be in-person, and you are encouraged to attend the live lectures when possible. If this is generally not feasible for you, or makes you uncomfortable, please get in touch. Additionally, lectures will be recorded on zoom, and uploaded on the 3.029 <a href="https://canvas.mit.edu/courses/13469" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">canvas page</a>.</p></li><li><p>We will be piloting a custom web-based platform to deliver the lecture and reading notebooks for the class, which you can access here: <a href="https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://dmse-mit.github.io/3029/</a>. Feel free to peruse the site, but we will also spend some time navigating it together tomorrow.</p></li><li><p>We will reserve <a href="https://canvas.mit.edu/courses/13469" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">canvas</a> use for i) class-wide announcements, ii) accessing the zoom recordings, and iii) submitting/grading of assignments.</p></li><li><p>Finally, we have set up a <a href="https://mit-3029-sp22.slack.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Slack workspace</a> for the class for interactions outside the regularly-scheduled lecture and office hours. You should be receiving an invite to join from me shortly.</p></li></ul><p>See you tomorrow!<br>
<!-- -->George</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>welcome</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>